http://www.sessionmusic.co.uk/pages/privacy-policy

Instruments
Karaoke Discs (Multi Packs)
Karaoke Discs (Single)
Instruments
Karaoke Discs (Multi Packs)
Karaoke Discs (Single)
View less
Updated 30.4.18We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). 1. We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service and information about your products and services.
We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us. The type of information we will collect about you includes: • your name • address • phone number • email address • credit/debit card details We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.
Using your personal Information2.1 Personal data about our customers is an important part of our business and we shall only use your personal data for the following purposes and shall not keep such personal data longer than is necessary to fulfill these purposes2.1.1 To help us identify you when you contact us2.1.2 To help us identify accounts, services and / or products which you could have from us or selected partners from time to time. We may do this by automatic means using a scoring scoring system, which uses the personal data you have provided and /or any information we hold about you and Personal Data from third party agencies (including credit reference agencies.)
2.1.3.To help us to administer and to contact you about improved administration of any accounts, services and products we have provided before, do provide now or will or may provide in the future.2.1.4.To allow us to carry out marketing analysis and customer profiling (including with transactional information), conduct research, including creating statistical and testing information.2.1.5.To help to prevent and detect fraud or loss.2.1.6.To allow us to contact you in any way (including mail, email, telephone, visit, text or multimedia messages) about products and services offered by us and selected partners unless you have previously asked us not to do so.2.1.7.We may monitor and record communications with you (including phone conversations and emails) for quality assurance and compliance.2.1.8.We may check your details with fraud prevention agencies. If you provide false or inaccurate information and we suspect fraud, we will record this.2.2.We will not disclose your Personal Data to any third party except in accordance with this Privacy Policy.2.3.We may allow other people and organisations to use Personal Data we hold about you in the following circumstances:2.3.1.If we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired or are in the process of being acquired by a third party, in which case Personal Data held by us, about our customers, will be one of the transferred assets.2.3.2.If we have been legitimately asked to provide information for legal or regulatory purposes or as part of legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.2.3.3.We employ companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf and we may disclose your Personal Data to these parties for the purposes set out in clause 2.1 or, for example, for fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links) and providing customer service. Those parties are bound by strict contractual provisions with us and only have access to Personal Data needed to perform their functions, and may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the Data Protection Act 1998 and the GDPR. From time to time, these other people and organisations to whom we may pass your Personal Data may be outside the European Economic Area. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your Personal Data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Data Protection Act 1998 and the GDPR.2.4.Where you give us Personal Data on behalf of someone else, you confirm that you have provided them with the information set out in this Privacy Policy and that they have not objected to such use of their Personal Data.2.5.In connection with any transaction which we enter into with you:2.5.1.We, and other companies in our group, may carry out credit and fraud prevention checks with one or more licensed credit reference and fraud prevention agencies. We and they may keep a record of the search. Information held about you by these agencies may be linked to records relating to other people living at the same address with whom you are financially linked. These records will also be taken into account in credit and fraud prevention checks. Information from your application and payment details of your account will be recorded with one or more of these agencies and may be shared with other organisations to help make credit and insurance decisions about you and members of your household with whom you are financially linked and for debt collection and fraud prevention. This includes those who have moved house and who have missed payments.2.5.2.If you provide false or inaccurate information to us and we suspect fraud, we will record this and may share it with other people and organisations. We, and other credit and insurance organisations, may also use technology to detect and prevent fraud.2.5.3.If you need details of those credit agencies and fraud prevention agencies from which we obtain and with which we record information about you, please write to our Data Protection Manager Session Music, Guildford Road, Normandy Surrey GU3 2DAWe do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties and will not share your personal information with third parties other than as set out below.
3.Protecting InformationWe have strict security measures to protect Personal Data.3.1.We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.3.2.All processing of payments online are done via our third party web provider Shopify and the bank3.3.We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.3.4.It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.
How we share your personal information and with whom
We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
We may disclose your personal information to other third parties, as follows:
to service providers who help us run the Site and our services, solely for the purposes of running the Site or administering our business. These third parties currently include Shopify (who host our servers);
to our advertising agencies and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you;
subject to your consent, to third parties who may offer products or services that may interest you;
to report offences under the Computer Misuse Act 1990;
if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our users will be one of the transferred assets;
if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or any other terms or agreements.
We may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.
Your Rights
You may at any time ask us to remove your personal details from our records by sending an email to marketing@sessionmusic.co.uk
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes, and give you an opportunity to opt-out of marketing at the point of data collection. You can also exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting us at marketing@sessionmusic.co.uk
You are also entitled to correct, review, update or change your personal information at any time.
Links to other websites
Our Site may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our Site, you should note that we do not have any control over those other websites and therefore we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such websites. Such websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes here. However, we will not make any material changes to the way we process your personal information without first seeking your consent. You should review this Privacy Policy from time to time.
Access to information
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to an administration fee of £10 as a contribution to our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
If you wish to exercise your right of access, please send your request to: marketing@sessionmusic.co.uk
Contact us
If you have any concerns about material which appears on the Site, or any questions, comments or requests regarding our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy, please contact us at marketing@sessionmusic.co.uk or at our postal address of Session Music, Guildford Road, Normandy Surrey GU3 2DA or use the “Contact Us” page on the Site
If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should contact us by emailing sales@sessionmusic.co.uk or calling 01483 811137
